connectify.me 2012-10-29

# Privacy Policy - Connectify

####  EFFECTIVE DATE 10/18/2009; UPDATED 12/3/2009  

This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices with respect to information we collect about our customers and visitors who; 

  1. Use, browse, shop at any of the CONNECTIFY Website, including our regional websites (referred to collectively as “our Site”) to make purchases or obtain free downloads and 
  2. Register to use our Site. If the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy conflict or create a discrepancy with the terms of a private contractual agreement you have with CONNECTIFY, such as the End User License Agreement, the private contractual terms will control.

###  Commitment to Privacy  

As a security software producer, CONNECTIFY knows that you care about how your information is used and shared. We respect your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the use of your information is important to us. We want to make sure that you understand the type of information we collect about you, how it is used and the safeguards we use to protect it. This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal information you share with us. 

###  What Information Does CONNECTIFY Collect?  

The type of information that we collect and retain depends upon your interaction with our Site. Here is a short overview of the two main types of interactions. 

  1. Information You Give Us. We collect the personally identifiable information you provide to us on our Site, including your name, address, email address, telephone number, and if you pay by credit card, your account information when you:
    * Create a user account, place an order, register a product (information we collect is necessary to complete the transaction and so that we can keep you informed about CONNECTIFY products and services, such as your name, last name, e-mail address, and country).
    * Requesting product support or other services (information we collect is necessary to, provide support and to respond to queries such as your name and address and information about your computer hardware, software (including your License Number), and the nature of the problem you are experiencing)
    * Participate in surveys (information we collect may include demographic information such as age, gender and number of household members)

You have the final decision on whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. However, if you do not wish to provide information needed for a transaction, you may not be able to complete it. 

  2. Information Collected and Stored Automatically. When you interact with CONNECTIFY we may maintain a record of the following types of information.
    * Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address or other technical information such as a referring web site, if any, and the path you take through CONNECTIFY Sites when you visit us online.
    * The date and time, the internet address of the website from which you link directly to our website.
    * The name of the file or the words you search, and the browser you use to access our website.

The information collected and stored automatically by our Site is used to measure the number of visitors to various sections of our Site and to identify system performance or for server issues. We also use this information to help us expand the coverage of our Site and to make our Site more useful. This information is not linked by us to personally identifiable information and we do not disclose this in a form that personally identifies you, except in cases where we must provide IP addresses to certain credit card processors in connection with the processing of your credit card transaction. You may want to contact your credit card provider with any questions regarding the transactional information they require. 

###  Do We Use Cookies?  

“Cookies” are small pieces of unique information, sent by a website, that are stored on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser. Cookies enable a website to tailor information presented to you based on your browsing preferences. CONNECTIFY uses cookies to personalize your pages at our Site, when you seek service & support or to remember you when you register for products or services. CONNECTIFY may also use cookies to track your visit to our Site. While our web servers may automatically log your IP address, the type of information we collect pertains to how you navigate, browse and purchase on our Site. This information is not personally identifiable, and we do not correlate this information with your personal information. 

If you do not want us to store this information or if you are using a public computer, the “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or how to disable cookies altogether. However, rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some of the products and/or services at our Site. 

###  How Do We Use the Information We Collect?  

The personal information we collect is generally used to process your requests and transactions, to provide you with high quality service, to tell you about opportunities we think will be of interest to you, to customize your experience on our Site and to understand your needs so that we may provide you with the most suitable products and services. For example, we may use your personal information to help us: 

  * Provide you with information about alerts, product upgrades, new products, services, research on future product ideas or improvements;
  * Send newsletters, informative e-mails or other information which has the nature of business announcements. CONNECTIFY reserves the right to use customers’ contact information to send them information it deems important for the full utilization of its products and services. Every registered customer may choose not to receive such information from CONNECTIFY by simply selecting the opt-out checkbox when registering your software (with the exception of messages which are necessary for the functionality of our products and services)
  * Create content that is relevant to you
  * Provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you
  * Assist us in creating better, customized products and services to meet your needs
  * Allow you to purchase and download products, obtain access to services or otherwise engage in activities you select
  * Help you quickly find software, services, or product information important to you
  * Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you chose to do so
  * Notify you about changes to our service

###  With Whom Do We Share Your Information?  

CONNECTIFY does not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. Under certain circumstances and from time to time, CONNECTIFY may share your personally identifiable information with third parties as set forth below. In such circumstances, we provide only the information necessary to perform the function or to provide the service for which it has been shared. These third parties are required to keep the information confidential and are not permitted to use the personal information provided by us for any purpose, except as authorized by CONNECTIFY. 

CONNECTIFY may share your information with third parties such as: 

  * Service Providers: We may share your personally identifiable information with trusted service providers who provide operational or other support services to our Customers or who perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include providers who fulfill orders, ship products, process transactions (including credit card transactions), distribute e-mails, conduct research or statistical analysis or provide other marketing assistance. It may be necessary to share user personal information with these service providers in order to allow them to provide their services. You have the right not to provide the requested information, but in such case you may not be able to receive these services. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service and we require that they keep the personal information of our customers secure and confidential and comply with the Act and all other applicable laws. We also require that these contractors use our customers’ personal information only on behalf of CONNECTIFY and do not disclose them to third parties or use them for any other purpose. 
  * Local Partners, Distributors and Resellers: We may share your personal information, such as your e-mail contact, with selected local CONNECTIFY partners, distributors and resellers so that they can contact you, either on our behalf or for their own account, about our products, services or offers that we believe are important to you or your business and to provide you a local technical and customer support.
  * Other Disclosures: We may share your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is:
    * authorized by law or necessary to comply with a legal process; 
    * in response to legal claims; 
    * required to protect and defend the rights, property or legitimate interests of CONNECTIFY (including the enforcement of our agreements)
    * necessary to protect personal safety, property or other rights of CONNECTIFY and its customers or employees
    * an integral part of a sale of all or part of our business. 

###  Consent  

By providing us with your personal information when registering at our Site or when you obtain or use any of our products or services, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure by CONNECTIFY of your personal information as provided in this Privacy Policy. Your consent includes the retention of personal information that is collected through our Site, including your personal information that you submit through a registration process, for as long as you are registered at our Site or you are a user of CONNECTIFY products and services, and for a reasonable time thereafter, unless and until you withdraw your consent. 

###  Security  

CONNECTIFY is committed to maintaining the security of information under our control. We have taken security measures, consistent with industry practices, to protect your personal information. To try to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information, we have put in place industry-accepted physical, technical and administrative practices to safeguard and secure the information we collect. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. To protect the confidentiality of this category of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. If other people have access to your e-mail, they may be able to change information about your user profile. You should not use an e-mail account operated by an employer because many employers have the legal right to access such e-mail accounts. If you share a computer with anyone, always log out before leaving our Site to protect access to your information from subsequent users. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Credit card information is transmitted using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption. We use industry-accepted encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions and have implemented commercially available to guard against unauthorized access to any personal information that is stored electronically by CONNECTIFY. We restrict access to personal information about you to those CONNECTIFY employees who need to know the information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 

Unfortunately, no transmission of information over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to our Site from your PC or the Internet Service Provider, and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to ensure its security on our system and to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

###  How Can You Correct Inaccuracies in the Information?  

We strive to maintain the accuracy of the information collected through our Site. Furthermore, we believe that the individual is invaluable in ensuring that data is complete and accurate. We will provide you with access to personally identifiable information you provide through our Site for as long as we maintain that information in a readily accessible format. Similarly, we permit and encourage you to correct inaccuracies in the information you submit to us through our Site. If you believe that CONNECTIFY does not have your current personal information, you can update it by contacting CONNECTIFY Support Team at support@connectify.me. 

If you have provided personal information to CONNECTIFY you may ask us to advise you of the scope of information CONNECTIFY processes about you, the purpose and nature of the processing and the recipients of the information. 

###  CONNECTIFY Update Bulletin and Other E-mail Communications  

If you do not wish to continue receiving our e-mail newsletters, bulletins, or other information from CONNECTIFY, you can opt-out at any time by responding to any e-mail you receive from us and writing the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line of the response. Please be aware that our e-mails may include important or useful information about your product, including information about your License Number or the status of your orders or accounts, and that we do not allow our customers to opt-out of communication that is required for the functionality of our products and services. 

###  Links to Other Companies  

Periodically, our Site may contain links to and from websites of our business partners, distributors, resellers, advertisers or other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies which you should read before you submit any personal data to these websites. We disclaim any liability for the data processing activities of our business partners, distributors and resellers, all of which act as independent data processing controllers. 

###  Co-branded Websites  

We also link to co-branded websites that are maintained by CONNECTIFY and one or more of our business partners. When you submit information to one of our co-branded websites, you may be submitting it to both CONNECTIFY and our business partners. Please note that the privacy policies of these co-branded websites may differ from this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on any co-branded website to which you link, and we disclaim any liability for the data processing activities of our business partners which act as independent data processing controllers. 

###  Children  

We encourage parents to take an active interest in their children’s use of the Internet. Our Site is not targeted to children younger than 13 years of age. CONNECTIFY does not knowingly collect or store information of children younger than 13. Visitors who are under the age of 13 may use our Site only with the supervision and consent of a parent or guardian. None of the products or services available through Our Site may be purchased by anyone less than 18 years of age. 

###  Discussion Groups and Forums  

Please remember that information you submit in a discussion group or forum at our Site will be deemed public information and is not confidential. There is a risk in such communication venues that various information and data can be collected and used by others. Please be careful and responsible when you are on-line. 

###  Changes of Privacy Policy  

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. However, we will alert you that changes have been made by indicating at the top of the Privacy Policy the date it was last updated. If we ever make a material change to how we use the information you provide and the new uses are unrelated to uses we disclose in this Policy, we will communicate the changes in a prominent notice on our Site prior to its implementation and provide you the opportunity to change your marketing preferences to opt-out of such use. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

###  Language  

This Privacy Policy was originally prepared in the English language. Although CONNECTIFY may provide one or more translations for your convenience, the English version will control in the case of any conflict or discrepancy. 

###  Contact Us  

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@connectify.me](mailto:support@connectify.me)
